[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which vehicle can also transport data?", "correct_answer": "Bus", "incorrect_answers": ["Ship", "Car", "Plane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dakota Fanning plays Richards daughter in the 2006 film Babel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What accident caused partial paralysis of Sylvester Stallones face, resulting in his famous pronunciation and lip droop?", "correct_answer": "a accident at his birth", "incorrect_answers": ["He was kicked in the face while practicing martial arts.", "He was accidentally shot in the face while shooting a movie scene.", "a car accident"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Pixar-created family of superheroes?", "correct_answer": "The Incredibles", "incorrect_answers": ["X-Men", "The Justice League", "Fantastic Four"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did the glass lizard, also known as glass snake, get its interesting name?", "correct_answer": "It breaks easily.", "incorrect_answers": ["It can climb on glass.", "Its eyes are glass-like.", "It is almost transparent."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bases corrode metal.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In medical parlance, what is an A-line?", "correct_answer": "Arterial line", "incorrect_answers": ["Anatomic line", "Analog line", "Afferent line"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The action in the 2001 movie The Brotherhood of the Wolf takes place in what country?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Germany", "USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name for a band of the celestial sphere centered on the ecliptic and encircling the sky?", "correct_answer": "Zodiac", "incorrect_answers": ["Vernal Equinox", "Photosphere", "Corona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the winner of the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor for 1995.", "correct_answer": "Pauly Shore for Jury Duty", "incorrect_answers": ["Kyle MacLachlan for Showgirls", "Kevin Costner for Waterworld", "Sylvester Stallone for Assassins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following people is generally at the highest risk of suicide?", "correct_answer": "A divorced, unemployed man living alone", "incorrect_answers": ["A depressed housewife with a disabled child", "An anxious stockbroker", "A single mother with 4 children who is on welfare"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before marrying June Carter, singer Johny Cash was married to whom?", "correct_answer": "Vivian Cash", "incorrect_answers": ["Roseanne Cash", "Carlene Cash", "Violet Cash"]}]